http://edsitement.neh.gov/about/conditions

Search this Section
EDSITEment is a project of the National Endowment for the Humanities
Facebook
Twitter
Conditions Of Use
Disclaimer for External Links and Non-Federal Resources
EDSITEment contains a variety of links to other websites and references to resources available through government, nonprofit, and commercial entities. External links to websites from the "EDSITEment" website and references to non-federal resources are provided solely for informational purposes and the convenience of the user. The National Endowment for the Humanities does not control, review, approve, or endorse these sites, nor does the Endowment control, review, approve, or endorse these resources. These other sites may collect data or personal information. Once you link to another site, you are subject to the privacy policy of the new site. If you decide to access any site linked to this site, you do so entirely at your own risk. In addition, the external links and non-federal resources are in no way intended to represent an exhaustive listing.
Opinions and Interpretations
The "EDSITEment" website site contains information gathered from many different sources. The opinions and interpretations expressed in the website do not necessarily state or reflect the views or policies of the United States Government, or any agency, contractor, or subcontractor thereof.
Providing personal information on the Internet is completely voluntary, yet different websites may do different things with that information. Before providing any personal information, you should familiarize yourself with the Privacy Policy of the site collecting the information. Please read carefully our Privacy Policy, and the privacy policy of any third-party website to which you provide personal information.
Who We Are
"EDSITEment" is a World Wide Website for humanities education developed and maintained by the National Endowment for the Humanities, a federal government agency, for the benefit of parents, students, and teachers.
EDSITEment provides access to educational websites which, as judged by a panel of experts, were selected solely on the basis of educational excellence in the humanities and high-quality website design. EDSITEment is not a complete course in any humanities discipline, nor does it attempt to provide comprehensive coverage of the humanities. EDSITEment does not prescribe a specific course of study nor advocate any educational theory. EDSITEment is intended solely to be an educational resource for teachers, parents, and students.
The text, images and other materials in the websites linked to EDSITEment were reviewed by a panel of experts and found to be educationally appropriate for users of all ages. Recognizing that the World Wide Web is a dynamic, interactive, and exploratory environment for humanities education, the humanities content of the linked sites may change and expand over time. The National Endowment for the Humanities reserves the right to terminate any link or linking program at any time.
Copyright
Lesson Plans. Except where otherwise noted, NEH holds the copyright for lesson plans and student resources, and licenses such content under a Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International License. This License allows subsequent users to copy, distribute, transmit, and adapt the content and requires such users to attribute the work to NEH.
The open source works noted above are licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International License.
Images and Other Materials. Apart from the lesson plans, images and other materials on this website may be protected by copyright laws and other restrictions. NEH expressly prohibits the copying of protected materials on this website, except for the purposes of fair use as defined in the copyright law. Please contact edsitement@neh.gov for further clarification.
User's Obligation to Obey Applicable Laws
While many of the images and documents in websites linked with EDSITEment may be in the public domain, others may be protected under copyright, trademark, and other intellectual property laws of the United States and foreign countries. Such laws generally prohibit (subject to civil and criminal penalties) the unauthorized reproduction, distribution, adaptation, display, and performance of protected works. It is the user's obligation to comply with these applicable laws, including, where necessary, seeking the advice of counsel regarding the application of the fair use doctrine to the proposed educational use of materials. Other federal, state, and local laws that may apply to the use of materials linked with EDSITEment are defamation, misappropriation, invasion of privacy, and/or publicity rights.
Liability
Neither the United States Government nor any agency thereof, nor any of their employees, nor any of their contractors, subcontractors, or their employees: (1) make any warranty, express or implied, or assume any legal liability or responsibility for the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any text, image, or materials in any website linked with the "EDSITEment" website; or (2) represent that their use would not defame or violate or infringe upon the rights, including, without limitation, copyrights, trademarks, or any other intellectual property rights, moral rights, publicity rights, or privacy rights of any other person or entity.
Acceptance of Terms
By using this site, you signify your assent to these policies. If you do not agree to these conditions, please do not use this site.
Comments
The Endowment welcomes your comments or questions about the "EDSITEment" website. Because of the volume of usage on the site, however, the Endowment may not be able to respond directly to your inquiry.
Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998
Pursuant to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998, the agent to receive notification of claimed infringement is:
